Syehbi Herbian

Web Developer

Kota Tangerang | 6285155227287 | syehbiherbian@gmail.com



Summary

Hard-working Web developer, with 4 years experience, Building websites, and applications with Laravel Framework and Django Framework. Developed a company profile website, the marketplace for an online tutorial, and a website rental system. Experience with Angular JS, React, NuxtJS (server side rendering from Vue JS), Java Spring, Micro Service Architecture.

Community Involvement

- Startup Student Mentoring -Student Job Asociation
- Volunteer Indonesia E-commerce Summit & Expo

Professional Experience

Software Engineer-Front End

2019 - now

2019 - 2019

RCTI+ - Member Of MNC Group

- Build Application WEB for Video On Deman(VOD) and live streaming for MNC Media
- Develop high quality, maintainable and scalable systems to effectively solve challenges.
- Create and support a productive and innovative team. This includes working with peers, managers, and teams.
- Collaborate with UI/UX design team & Product team
- Developing new user-facing features using Laravel for Server Side Rendering
- Translating designs and wireframes into high quality code

- 1. laravel
- 2. scrum
- 3. bootstrap
- 4. JWPlayer

Skills

Python

Project Management

Leadership

Nuxt IS

Next IS

React IS

MySQL

Vue IS

Laravel

REST API

Create REST API with Laravel & Django Framework

Linux

Related Skill:

- 5. React IS

FullStack Developer

Telkom SIgma

- Development tasks of in-house program assigned by customer
- Responsible day to day maintenance of current in house developed program
- Analyzed for data, normalization, building relational of database and stored into structured and most optimized data to cover effectiveness of query
- Build Passport Application with micro service architecture, tech stack for backend Java Spring and frontend with Angular JS

Related Skill:

- 1. Java Spring
- 2. MySQL
- 3. docker
- 4. micro services architecture
- 5. Angular JS

Co-Founder & Technical Leader

Desember 2016 - Februari 2019

Cilsy Fiolution Responsibilities

- Manage IT team to deliver the product
- Research new technology for the new feature

Django

- Work with Product owner for requirement new feature
- Plan and prioritize product feature backlog and development for the product
- Collaborate with UI/UX design team & Product team

Related Skill:

- 1. Laravel
- 2. mysql
- 3. Video|S
- 4. jquery
- 5. Bootstrap

Backend Developer

March 2017 - November 2017

GIT

PT Oprent Teknologi Indonesia

Responsibilities

- Maintenance Website
- Create REST API with Django Framework

Related Skill:

- -Django
- -PostgreSql
- -REST API

Web Developer

September 2016 - Februari 2017

PT Elven Digital Indonesia

Responsibilities

- Creating a custom web site responsiveness (Laravel Framework, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, jQuery, JS angle, etc.
- Upload the website data to Server
- And others according to the needs of management companies

Related Skill:

- 1. Laravel
- 2. Jquery
- 3. MySQL
- 4. Bootstrap
- 5. CSS

Web Developer (Freelance)

2016 - 2016

PT Telkom Indonesia

Responsibilities

- Maintenance Website(Codeigniter Framework)
- Create a new feature

Education

Universitas Pamulang 2013 - 2018

Bachelor Degree In Computer Science

GPA 3.31

SMK Negeri 4 Tangerang 2010 - 2013

Software Engineering Faculty

Portfolio

Aplikasi Paspor Imigrasi





Aplkasi Penerbitan Paspor Aplkasi Penerbitan Paspor

Portfolio

www.cilsy.id

online platform Tutorial



Cllsy.id

Portfolio

pesanlab.com



pesan lab

Portfolio

rctiplus.com is platform for video on demand and live streaming from MNC MEDIA







login

homepage

detail program